{
    "subject": "resource/The_Smiling_Lieutenant",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "United States",
    "human_readable": "The Smiling Lieutenant was from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9759823083877563,
            "question": "Is The Smiling Lieutenant American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8122891187667847,
            "question": "Where was The Smiling Lieutenant born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8073884844779968,
            "question": "What country is The Smiling Lieutenant from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7234170436859131,
            "question": "What nationality is The Smiling Lieutenant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6800609827041626,
            "question": "Who created The Smiling Lieutenant character?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5683815479278564,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about The Smiling Lieutenant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5457319021224976,
            "question": "Where might The Smiling Lieutenant be located now?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41996291279792786,
            "question": "Is there a film or book called 'The Smiling Lieutenant'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06582812964916229,
            "question": "Can you give me an example of another famous person from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.010760175995528698,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of American characters in fiction?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Smiling Lieutenant was from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7616_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give me an example of another famous person from the United States?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7616_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a film or book called 'The Smiling Lieutenant'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7616_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might The Smiling Lieutenant be located now?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7616_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7616_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7616_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7616_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7616_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7616_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7616_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7616_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7616_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7616_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7616_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"The Smiling Lieutenant is a 1931 American Pre-Code musical comedy film,\" which supports the statement that \"The Smiling Lieutenant was from United States.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states the film was released by Paramount Pictures.  Paramount Pictures was an American studio, making it highly probable the film itself originated in the US.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}